(Leonard:)Hey, ready for lunch?
Oh, one sec.
(Sheldon:)Is that the prototype drive
system for the high-G rover?
(Howard:)No, Bernadette
got me a Fitbit
(Howard:)so she can track
how much I'm exercising.
(Leonard:)That'll teach her to care
about your health.
(Howard:)I can't wait to see the look
on her face when I die young.
(Raj:)When was the last actual
exercise you got?
(Howard:)The other day, when
(Howard:)she tried to put that Fitbit
on me and I ran away from her.
(Sheldon:)According to a recent study,
(Sheldon:)simply thinking about exercise,
even while sitting still,
(Sheldon:)can have physical benefits.
(Sheldon:)For all you know,
I could be exercising right now.
(Raj:)Are you?
Eh, I'll do it tomorrow.
(Leonard:)It wouldn't be the worst thing
(Leonard:)if we were more active.
Oh. You make
an excellent point.
(Howard:)Ooh, I think
I'm getting a runner's high!
♪ Our whole universe
was in hot, dense state ♪